马德·德·迪奥斯。
Madre de Dios.
现在就保护我们。
Protect us now.
莱尔德似乎在拿... ...大部分都打在他的肩膀和手肘上。
Laird seems to be taking... ... most of those blows on his shoulders and elbows.
珀金斯的左手好像有点动。
Perkins appears to be pulling his left a bit.
他的手可能在第二回合受伤了。
He just might have hurt that hand back in round two.
如果你来晚了，珀金斯在第二轮数到八的时候就倒下了。
If you joined us late, Perkins was down in round two for an eight count.
第六回合结束了。
And there's the end of round six.
你付电话费了吗?
Did you pay the phone?
我要借。
I gotta borrow.
反对什么?
Against what?
我的房子很干净。
Well, my house is clear.
几乎。
Almost.
没有机会。不是那栋房子。
No chance. Not that house.
这是一个好房子。这是一栋很棒的房子。
It's a good house. It's a terrific house.
你答应过我你会找到合适的人。
You promised me you'd find somebody.
我说我会试试。
I said I would try.
我得把那房子卖掉。
I gotta get rid of that house.
那你为什么不把它给别人呢?
Well, why don't you give it to somebody?
我试过了，那家伙说也许我可以把车扔进去。
I tried and the guy said maybe if I'd throw in my car.
准备好支付电话费或电话答录费了吗?
Had enough ready for the phone bill or the answering service?
这是一个好房子。但不是两者都有。
It's a good house. But not both.
我得把它处理掉，仅此而已。所以我付了服务费。
Gotta get rid of it, that's all. So I paid the service.
现在我们可以得到一条消息。
Now we can get a message.
来电仍然有效。
Incoming still works.
如果我们想喊出来呢?
What if we want to call out, you know?
回个信息什么的?
Return a message or something?
明天早上有个约会。
Got an appointment in the morning.
是关于什么的?
What's it about?
到目前为止还没有任何问题。只是个约会。
It's not about anything so far. Just an appointment.
嗯…你可以留着它，不是吗?
Well... You can keep it, can't you?
是的。
Yeah.
我想我今晚要去水槽里。
I'm going in the tank tonight, I think.
是的。
Yeah.
你知道匹兹堡的交易吗?
You know the Pittsburgh deal?
我们放在干文件里的那个?
The one we put in the dry file?
消失的那个?
The one that disappeared?
是的。
Yeah.
昨晚，我和伯尼在吃晚饭，一个男人跳着华尔兹走过来。
Well, last night, Bernie and I were having dinner, and a guy waltzes over to the table.
然后把这个扔到我腿上。
And drops this right in my lap.
是那个女人。
It's the woman.
Quemando的女人。
Quemando's woman.
她在镇上的每个围栏里都放了一个。
She's put one of those out to every fence in town.
就像电话卡。
Like calling cards.
她想把我们的面包卖出去。
She's trying to sell our bread.
没有错吧?
There's no mistake?
不。
No.
还没有。
Not yet.
我们找些士兵来。
Let's get some soldiers.
希基先生还是博格斯先生?
Mr. Hickey or Mr. Boggs?
吻痕。
Hickey.
博格斯先生不来了?
Mr. Boggs won't be joining us?
博格斯先生今天上午在办公室。
Mr. Boggs is in the office this morning.
有什么能帮你的，赖斯先生?
How can we help you, Mr. Rice?
你好。
Hello.
是的。
Yeah.
确定。
Sure.
正确的。
Right.
不，你打给蒙特，然后我们去找肥仔。
No, you call Monte, then we'll get Fatboy.
正确的。
Right.
尼克?我可以打电话给我妈妈吗?
Nick? Can I call my Mom?
当然,亲爱的。
Sure, honey.
这件事应该做得很精细。
It ought to be delicately done.
我已经有一段时间没见到她了。
It's been some time since I've seen her.
只要找到她，就够了。
Just to find her, is all that's really necessary.
我不想让你联系她，明白吗?
I don't want you to contact her, you understand?
她可能会回避。
She might shy away.
自由裁量权。
Discretion.
我是说，你知道这类事情。
You know the sort of thing, I mean.
找到她在哪里，然后告诉你。
Just find out where she is and let you know.
精确。
Precisely.
杰克?
Jack?
是吗?
Yeah?
我要坐GTO;特殊的。
I'm taking the GTO; the special.
蒙特?
Monte?
钥匙在遮阳板上面。
The keys are atop the visor.
你知道这可能需要一些时间。
You understand this may take some time.
我相信不会太久。
Well, not too very long, I trust.
这就留下了钱的问题。
That leaves the question of money.
每天200英镑，外加费用。
Two hundred a day plus expenses.
我明白了。
I see.
为通货膨胀尽自己的一份力量。
Doing your bit for inflation.
那只是个玩笑。
It was just a joke.
很好。
Very well.
我的电话号码就在其中一张纸上。
My answering service number is on one of those pieces of paper.
有消息就打给我。
Call when you have something to report.
500美元。
Five hundred dollars.
作为预付款。
As an advance.
证明我的诚意。
A demonstration of my sincerity.
这就足够了吗?
Is that sufficient?
我想是的，赖斯先生。
I think so, Mr. Rice.
嗯…你好，希基先生。
Well... Arrivederci, Mr. Hickey.
我们会跟你聊的。
We'll be talking to you.
我们的工作。
We're working.
听你这么说我很高兴。
I'm glad to hear it.
我不想打扰你。
I hate to bother you.
没事，只是想休息一下。
It's all right, just wanted to take a minute.
看到这个女孩了吗?
See this girl?
什么，她放出去了吗?
What, does she put out?
她是来做生意的，笨蛋。
She's business, dummy.
玛丽·简... ...鲍尔。
Mary Jane... ...Bower.
是的。
Yeah.
跟我说说她吧。
Tell me about her.
有个叫赖斯的小甜嘴想让我们找到她。
Some little sweet lips by the name of Rice wants us to find her.
对什么?
What for?
浪漫的联系。
A romantic connection.
"甜唇"让人欲罢不能啊?
A switch-hitting Sweet Lips, huh?
好吧，别取笑客户。
Yeah, well don't make fun of the client.
我们要付5美元的定金。
We got a five bill retainer.
你觉得钱能让我神魂颠倒吗?
Do you think money turns my head around?
法罗，斯沃普，最后一个是什么?
Farrow, Swope and what's this last one?
凯》。我想那是西班牙语。
Kay Mundo. That's Spanish I think.
赖斯最后一次见到玛丽·简是什么时候?
When was the last time Rice saw Mary Jane?
三周前。
Three weeks ago.
我去见法罗。你去找蒂娜·斯沃普。
I'll see Farrow. You look up Tina Swope.
他们几年前是朋友。
They were friends a few years ago.
米饭不再喜欢它们了。
Rice don't like them anymore.
他只想要玛丽·简。
He just wants Mary Jane.
这是他的钱。
Well, it's his money.
是啊，有些是我们的。
Yeah, well some of it's gonna be ours.
听着，无论你什么时候跟这些火鸡说话，赖斯都不希望你提到他的名字。
Now, look, whenever you talk to any of these turkeys, Rice doesn't want you to mention his name.
Nyona怎么样?
How's Nyona?
Nyona谁?
Nyona who?
他们是可爱的。谢谢你！
They're lovely. Thank you.
不管是什么，我不想要，他也不想要。
Whatever it is, I don't want any, and neither does he.
他的墨镜还没戴上，他甚至还没醒。
His shades are still down, he isn't even awake yet.
你们这些骗子都一样。
You con-men are all alike.
他是谁?
Who is he?
你可以先说声"你好"
Well, you could start by saying "hello."
你好。
Hello.
公务员怎么样了?
How's the public servant?
我没有时间。
I don't have time.
他是谁?
Who is he?
我想他的名字是法罗。
I think his name is Farrow.
你在这里做什么?
What were you doing here?
跳过追踪女孩。
Skip tracing a girl.
他是个线索。
He's a lead.
通过查看邮箱，我确定法罗先生住在1338A公寓。
By checking the mailbox I determined that Mr. Farrow lived at Apartment 1338A.
因此，我运用了我不可思议的推理能力，走上楼梯来到了1338A公寓。
Therefore using my uncanny reasoning ability, I then proceeded up the stairs to Apartment 1338A.
别他妈开玩笑。
No goddamn jokes.
速记员注意，删掉希基的最后一句话和我的评论。
Note to stenographer, strike Hickey's last remark and my comment.
实话实说吧。
Just tell it straight.
什么吗?
Anything?
哦，蒂娜·斯沃普很久没见过玛丽·简了。年。
Oh, Tina Swope hadn't seen Mary Jane in a long time. Years.
他们以前和一对叫奎曼多的兄弟一起去。
They used to go with a couple of brothers named Quemando.
玛丽·简的男朋友因持械抢劫进了监狱。
Mary Jane's boyfriend went to the can for armed robbery.
这是一种艰难的赚钱方式。
A tough way to make a buck.
我们明天去见另一位奎曼多先生。
So we'll go see the other Mr. Quemando tomorrow.
是的。好吧。
Yeah. Okay.
法罗呢?
What about Farrow?
他被子弹夹住了。
He caught a bullet sandwich.
你说他死了是什么意思?是的，我找到他了。
What do you mean, he's dead? Yes, I found him.
你打算告诉我吗?
Were you gonna tell me about it?
通过查看邮箱，我确定克利夫顿·法罗先生住在1338A公寓。
Well, by looking at the mailbox, I determined that Mr. Clifton Farrow lived in Apartment 1338A.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
那家伙被炸飞了。抢劫吗?
Guy got blown up. Robbery?
看起来不像。
Doesn't look like it.
他只是开了门，收了钱。
He just opened up his door and got paid off.
谁拿了报纸?
Who's got the paper?
大部分都在你桌上。
Most of it's on your desk.
肖还有阿尔·希基的笔录。
Shaw's still got Al Hickey's transcript.
他找到了他。希是谁?
He found him. Who's Hickey?
他以前在霍伦贝克分部工作。
He used to be with the Hollenbeck Division.
嗨。
Hi.
这一点都不好笑，该死的。
That's not funny, goddamn it.
你的幽默感真可怜。
Your sense of humor is pathetic.
去你的。
God damn you.
别站在那儿，给我扔条毛巾。
Don't stand there, throw me a towel.
离开着。滚出去。
Quit gawking. Get outta here.
在另一个房间等着。
Wait in the other room.
我差点心脏病发作。
I almost had a heart attack.
你觉得你做的一切都很可爱。
You think everything you do is so cute.
这只是一种表达……在另一个房间等着。
It's just a way of saying... Just wait in the other room.
感觉好点了吗?
You feel better?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我想见你。
I want to see you.
三周以来第一次。
First time in three weeks.
我一直在努力工作。
I've been working very hard.
在谁?
On who?
别这样，亲爱的，放松点，好吗?
Come on, honey, loosen up, will you?
听着，我真的不喜欢这样。
Now, look, I really don't like this.
你走进来就像你住在这里一样。
You walk in here like you live here.
嗯，我做了。现在不是了。
Well, I did. Not any more.
你现在住在考克斯曼天堂。
You live in Coxman Heaven now.
你把我赶出去了。我得找个地方待着。
You threw me out. I gotta stay someplace.
和镇上所有的妓女。
With every hooker in town.
你和那个基佬搭档，你们在一起一定很幸福。
You and that fag partner, you must be very happy together.
听着，我真的很生气，你不会笑的。
Look, I'm really ticked off about this, and you're not gonna smile at it.
你想让我离开?
You want me to leave?
是的。
Yes.
好吧。
Okay.
我再给你一次机会。
I'll give you another chance.
今晚不行。它不是免费的。
Not tonight. It's not free.
你必须去争取。
You've got to earn it.
省省吧。
Spare me the drama.
一个叫蒂娜·斯沃普的女人，虽然她最近不太活跃。
A woman named Tina Swope, although she's been inactive recently.
一个叫布莱索的人。
A man named Bledsoe.
这很有可能。
There's a good possibility there.
我的前搭档，克里夫顿·法罗，我知道他一直在和这个人，这个女人谈判。
My former partner, Clifton Farrow, whom I know for a fact has been negotiating with this person, this woman.
你一定要小心他。
You must be very careful of him.
我们必须吗?大家都来了吗?
Must we? Is that everybody?
在西海岸，没有多少资源能够进行大规模的交易。
Not too many sources on the West Coast are capable of really huge transactions.
实际上涉及到多少?
How much is involved actually?
不管怎样，这是所有在这个区域买卖货币的人。
Anyway, that is everyone who fences currency or buys currency in this area.
伯尼，我还有一屋子人呢。
Bernie, I've got a houseful of people.
夏曼会杀了我的。
Charmaine is gonna kill me.
我可以帮你打电话给这些人，并建议... ...他们拒绝和这个女人做生意。
I could call these people for you and suggest... ...they refuse to do business with this woman.
你想接电话吗?
You want to pick this up?
你没听说过玛丽·简·鲍尔吗?
And you never heard of Mary Jane Bower?
直到现在还没有。我很抱歉。
Not until now, no. I'm sorry.
但是，如果我做了……原谅我。
But, if I do... Excuse me.
如果我还能帮上什么忙。
If I can be of any further help.
我们已经占用你足够多的时间了，呃……晚安，赖斯先生。
We've taken up enough of your time already, Mr. uh... Good night, Mr. Rice.
非常感谢你的诚实。
Thank you so much for your honesty.
他是在撒谎。
He's lying.
我知道。
I know.
还不重要。
Doesn't matter yet.
开始吧。
Get on this.
现在。今晚。
Now. Tonight.
不,不。
No, no.
如果丢了，就得报失窃。
If it's missing, it had to be reported stolen.
我要做个报告。
I've got a report to make.
哦，在这儿。在这里,看到了吗?
Oh, here it is. Here, see?
钥匙就是钥匙，夫人，除非能打开什么东西，否则别无它用。
Well, a key is still a key, ma'am, and nothing else until it opens something.
我会进行常规的锁测试。
I'll have run it through regular lock tests.
我今天下午就把它还给你，最迟明天。
I'll have it back to you this afternoon, tomorrow at latest.
如果有什么误会，我希望仅此而已，我有责任弄清真相。
If there has been a misunderstanding, and I hope that's all it is, it's my responsibility to get to the bottom of it.
少了一个体育迷。
One less sports fan.
她是个好女人。她有点糊涂，仅此而已。
Well, she's a nice lady. She's a little confused, that's all.
你出租公寓的时候，能给我们打个电话吗?
When you release the apartment, would you give us a call.
我想四处看看，只是碰碰运气，你知道，呃……我们也有工作要做，好吗?
I'd like to look around, just on the off chance, you know, uh... We've got a job to do, too, okay?
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
你一定要把钥匙还给我。
Be sure you return the key now.
是的，我只是需要更多的糖。
Yeah, I just need some more sugar.
什么吗?不。
Anything? No.
花店关门了。
The flower shop's closed.
请给我一份辣味热狗好吗?
May I have a chili dog, please?
两个。三。
Two. Three.
四杯加两杯可乐。
Make it four and two cokes.
在法罗家找到的。
Found this at Farrow's.
埃勒里女王。
Ellery Queen.
我也找到了。
I found those, too.
妈妈。把他们交出去真可耻。
Mother... Shame to turn 'em in.
是的。我们先给赖斯打电话吧。
Yeah. Let's call Rice first.
我做到了。他今天早上停止了服务。
I did. He checked his service off this morning.
关闭账户。没有转寄号码。
Closed the account. There's no forwarding number.
我们先吃吧。
Let's eat first.
在排水管下面?
Under the drainpipe, huh?
是的，在厨房。
Yeah, in the kitchen.
你知道这些名字吗?不。
You know any of these names? Nope.
草莓?我们不能帮你做所有的工作。
Hickey? We can't do all your work for you.
你是怎么进来的?
How did you get in?
走了。
Walked.
公寓是禁止入内的。
The apartment is off limits.
少废话了，说谢谢就行了。
Well, cut the crap out, just say thank you.
我们会找到它的。
We would have found it.
是的，当然，现在任何一个月都可以。
Yeah, sure, any month now.
我只是想帮你们。
Just trying to help you boys out.
好吧，好吧，我耳朵在流血。
All right, okay, my ears are bleeding.
看看吧。把它放一遍。让他们在里面放个混蛋。
Check it out. Run it through. Have them put a jerk in it.
正确的。
Right.
快点，小子?
Get right on that, will you kid?
是的，如果有什么情况请告诉我们。
Yeah, let us know if any thing comes up.
你把那张纸条复印了吗?
Did you make a copy of that note?
它在我的口袋里。帕帕达基斯这次会领先我们。
It's in my pocket. Papadakis will be ahead us this one.
我讨厌给他们任何东西。
I hate giving those guys anything.
是啊，但如果我们不这么做，他会让我们光着屁股，没有执照。
Yeah, but if we didn't, he'd have us bare-hineyed and no license.
我们只是在找玛丽·简。
We're only looking for Mary Jane.
是的，我知道，但是。
Yeah, I know, but still.
先生们，我能为你们效劳吗?
Can I help you gentlemen?
Quemando先生。
Mr. Quemando.
这是正确的。
That's right.
我们是私家侦探，奎曼多先生。
We're private investigators, Mr. Quemando.
也就是说你们不是真正的警察?
That mean you're not real cops?
我们在找玛丽·简·鲍尔。
We're looking for Mary Jane Bower.
你见过她吗?
You seen her?
我们只是在找她。没有麻烦。
We're just looking for her. There's no trouble.
我有五年没见过她了，也许更久了。
I haven't seen her in five years, maybe more.
我只是卖花。
I just sell flowers.
看来我们没有玛丽·简，也没有客户。
Looks like we got no Mary Jane and no client.
这就是你从法罗的笔记上抄下来的吗?
This is what you copied off Farrow's note?
有三个名字。地址在背面。
It's three names. Addresses on the back.
这些人看起来是认真的。
These guys look like they mean it.
让我们看看这个地址。
Let's check out this address.
告诉我们她在哪里。
Tell us where she is.
等一下。
Hold on a second.
这地方租给了玛丽·弗罗里达或弗罗里达。
Place is rented to a Marie Florida or Floreda.
几天没人见过她了。
Nobody's seen her in a few days.
四楼，后面。
Fourth floor, rear.
你开启了人格。
You turned on the personality.
是的。
Yeah.
还有50个大的。
And 50 big ones.
警察今天下午来过这里。没有人回家。
The cops were here this afternoon. Nobody home.
他们会回来的。
They'll be back.
是的。
Yeah.
看来你的钱花得值。
I see you got your money's worth.
如果有线索，她会通知我们的。
Yeah, if any heat shows up, she's gonna buzz us.
是的，希望如此，50美元。
Yeah, I hope so, for $50.
衣服不多。
Not many clothes.
家境贫寒的女孩
A girl of slender means.
是的。
Yes.
是的，谢谢你。
Yes, thank you.
是三个人。
It's three guys.
他们已经在这层了。
They're already on this floor.
这里!的行为!
Here! Behave!
该死的,狗娘养的!
Goddamn, son-of-a-bitch!
弗兰克，来吧。
Frank, will you come on.
我的上帝!
My God!
早上好。你好,firebug。
Good morning. Hello, firebug.
什么吗?
Anything?
我们收到一封挂号信。
We got a registered letter.
嗯，这看起来是个好消息。
Well, that looks like good news.
不，不完全是。
No, not really.
大米给了我们动力。他扣了我们的工资。
Rice has given us the gas. He's taken us off salary.
也许赖斯找到了玛丽·简。
Maybe Rice has found Mary Jane.
它没有这么说。
It doesn't say that.
我想他是被吓跑了。
I think he got scared off.
我喜欢你的风格。
I like your style.
我们还能做什么?
What the hell else we got to do?
听着，我回去找花店，你盯着赖斯。看看你能不能找到他。
Now look, I'll go back and see the florist, you stay on Rice. See if you can run him down.
你要穿这个?
You're gonna wear that?
艾尔。
Al.
你杀过人吗?
Did you ever kill anybody?
在美国。
In the United States.
因为我知道你是认真的，但是，我比你更了解这些人。
Because I know you mean it and everything, but, I know these guys better than I know you.
他们是士兵，仅此而已。
They're soldiers, that's all.
没有问题，没有时间问，没有谈话。
No questions, no time to ask, no talk.
警察更糟糕，更难以预测。
Cops are worse and less predictable.
如果你拔出枪，你就要做好杀人的准备。
If you pull a gun, you gotta be ready to kill somebody.
我跟你说，还是逃跑比较好。
I'm telling you it's better to run.
你做完了吗?
You finished?
你想告诉帕帕达基斯昨晚的事吗?
You want to tell Papadakis about last night?
嗯…
Well...
是的，先生，我喜欢你的风格。
Yes sir, I like your style.
找到帕帕达基斯的位置了吗?
You got a location on Papadakis?
那就把他找回来。
Well, get him back.
不，这是真的。
No, this is the real thing.
鲍勃。
Bob.
打个电话。
Put out a call.
把艾尔·希基和弗兰克·博格斯带来。
Bring in Al Hickey and Frank Boggs.
不，不是逮捕。
No, not an arrest.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell is going on here?
这些钱太热了，会在人行道上烧出一个洞。
This money is so hot, It'll burn a hole in the side walk.
死了两个人。匹兹堡有六人死亡。
Two people dead. Six dead in Pittsburgh.
每次有事情发生，你们俩都是幕后推手。
Every time something comes up, you two are part of the woodwork.
现在，我都想要。
Now, I want it all.
不要紧张你的气管。
Don't strain your windpipe.
我警告你，别胡闹。
I'm warning you, don't play around.
现在是谁在耍我们?我们把钱带来了。
Now who's playing around? We brought the money in.
你穿高跟鞋干什么?
What the hell were you doing heeled?
一盎司的预防。
An ounce of prevention.
我们到底有没有驾照?
We got a license or not?
到目前为止。
So far.
你需要什么?
Well, what do you need?
那花店呢?
What about the florist?
这是赖斯的线索。
It's a lead from Rice.
两条线索，两个死人。
Two leads, two dead men.
我们生活在乱世之中。
We live in troubled times.
没错，有很多社会动荡。你找到赖斯了吗?
That's right, there's a lot of social unrest. You find Rice?
这是下一件事。
That's the next thing.
我们也没有。
We haven't either.
那匹兹堡呢?
Well, what about Pittsburgh?
去年冬天，联邦储备银行，三名警卫被杀，三枚鱼雷被杀，司机带着一袋钱跑了。
Last winter, Federal Reserve Bank, three guards killed, three torpedoes killed, driver got away with a sack of money.
大账单。400000岁以上的老人。
Big bills. Over 400,000.
司机被打得满身是洞。
Driver got shot full of holes.
他们没找到钱，也没找到他女朋友。
They didn't find the money or his girlfriend.
-她叫什么名字?-我们不知道。
- What was her name? - We don't know that.
这有奖励吗?
Is there a reward for this?
二万五千年。
Twenty-five thousand.
我想从头再来一遍。
I want to go over this from the top.
你需要什么都行。
Anything you need.
玛丽·简弄不掉那个面团。
Mary Jane can't get rid of that dough.
账单太大了，花不了。
The bills are too big, can't spend it.
现在别为那个烦恼了，我们明天要去看比赛。
Don't bother with that now, we're going to the game tomorrow.
法罗是个推销员。
Farrow was a bagman.
她想以最低价卖掉那笔钱。我说我们要去看比赛，现在放松，享受这美好的…什么游戏?
She was trying to unload that dough at knock down rate... I said we're going to the game, now relax and enjoy this good... What game?
公羊,猎鹰。
Rams, Falcons.
哦,足球…我自己喜欢公羊队。
Oh, football... I favor the Rams myself.
我以为这场比赛的票已经卖光了。
I thought the game was a sell out.
它是。
It is.
我们找的是玛丽·简·鲍尔，不是罗曼·加布里尔。
We're looking for Mary Jane Bower, not Roman Gabriel.
两万五千美元。
Twenty-five thousand dollars.
你想要多大的赔率?
What kind of odds do you want?
公羊队?
On the Rams?
玛丽·简去看球赛了。
On Mary Jane being at the ballgame.
小屋,两个……
Hut, two...
我以为她今天会来。
I thought she'd show today.
试着制造轰动。
Try to make a hit.
让我看看。嗯,哦。
Let me see that. Hmm, oh.
法罗的手机旁边也写着同样的话。
Farrow had the same thing written beside his phone.
“公羊，猎鹰，再加一个。”
"Rams, Falcons, plus one."
还有这些座位。加1什么?
And these seats. Plus one what?
我猜是他们勾搭的人。
Whoever they are hitting on, I guess.
加一天?
Plus one day?
什么,明天?
What, tomorrow?
我不知道。
I don't know.
他们得定个时间。
Well, they'd have to set a time.
这张票可以打开它。
The ticket could key it.
游戏时间。
Game time.
这些席位。
These seats.
加上一天。是的,很好。
Plus one day. Yeah, well.
你好。
Hello.
天啊，不，我不想说话。
Oh, Christ no, I don't wanna talk.
我想睡觉。
I wanna sleep.
你好像只在睡前记得我的电话号码。
You only seem to remember my phone number at bedtime.
不得不在一场足球赛上工作。
Had to work at a football game.
你应该带我去的。
Well, you should have taken me.
当然，我们要做的任何事，都可以在棒球场做。
Sure, anything we gotta do, we can do at the ballpark.
我再看一遍。
Let me see that again.
像这样的贿赂只有两个人。
There's only two people in a buyoff like this.
三个很危险。为什么是第三个座位?
Three's dangerous. Why the third seat?
这是什么?
What is this?
什么都没有。上面写着"伊迪丝"
Nothing. Well, it says "Edith."
她有一部新手机。
She's got a new phone.
你又见到她了吗?
You seeing her again?
我不再付她赡养费了，她破产了。
I quit paying her the alimony and she's broke.
她需要帮助。
She needs help.
那个在韦斯特伍德有栋大房子的男朋友怎么样了?
Well, what happened to the boyfriend with the big house in Westwood?
不管是什么，昨天就发生了。
Whatever it was, it happened yesterday.
前一天晚上她还在那里。
She was still there the night before.
也许她找到了更大的…有个大房子的家伙。
Well, maybe she found a bigger... Guy with a bigger house.
不。
No.
她一直在要求回她原来的工作。
She's been asking for her old job back.
所以，他把她赶了出去。
So, he threw her out.
哎呀，我想知道为什么。
Gee, I wonder why.
好吧。
All right.
就这一辆马车?
This the only wagon?
好吧。
Okay.
别把这个给丢了，好吗?
And let's not lose this one, eh?
怎么啦？
What?
我的房子太小了。
My house was too small.
我知道，你告诉过我。
Yeah, I know, you told me.
嘿!
Hey!
好的，上士。
All right, Chief.
我们该怎么解释?
How are we supposed to explain this?
公羊队?
To the Rams?
警察。
The cops.
我会想办法的。
I'll think of something.
谢谢，先生。祝你好运，先生。
Thank you, sir. Good luck, sir.
越快越好，对吧。谢谢你！
Soon as you can, right. Thank you.
我们得到了一笔奖金。
We picked up a bonus.
他们没抓到那个女孩?
They didn't get the girl?
女孩没有出现。
The girl didn't show.
士兵们敲定了一笔交易。
The soldiers nailed a buy-off.
他们把推销员烧死了所以，还是没办法查出她在和谁打交道。
They burned up the bagman so, there's still no way to find out who she's dealing with.
我不想失去她。
I don't wanna lose her.
继续努力。
Keep pushing.
正确的。
Right.
这很乱，但我们别无选择。
It's messy, but we have no choice.
它属于我们。
It belongs to us.
最初的股份是我们的。
The original stake was ours.
如果我不能坚持原则，我就不能相信任何事情。
If I can't stick to a principle, I can't believe in anything.
正确的。
Right.
博格斯在法罗的手机旁看到了纸条。
Boggs saw the note by Farrow's phone.
我们觉得可能会找到玛丽·简。
We figured it might lead to Mary Jane.
我们觉得玛丽·简可能和法罗有约。
We figured Mary Jane might have had an appointment with Farrow.
你为什么不叫我们来?
Why didn't you call us in?
因为机会渺茫。
Cause it was a long shot.
鱼雷是怎么发现的?
How did the torpedoes find out about it?
他们逼出了奎曼多。
They beat it out of Quemando.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is this?
他们知道而我们不知道?
You know, they know and we don't?
你在体育馆打了一针，干掉了一个人。
You shoot up the Coliseum, blow off a hit.
一个推销员死了，洛杉矶到处都是尸体。
A bagman's dead, bodies lying all over LA.
你们两个笨蛋在大庭广众下表演。
You two bums made a grandstand play.
你应该在外面支援我们的。
Well, you should have been out there backing us up.
你有法罗的纸条。
You had Farrow's note.
别闹了。你们俩瞒着我们。
Come off it. You two held out on us.
你知道，我们也知道。
You know it and we know it.
充电吗?
Charging us?
我愿意......
I'd like to.
如果我想出别的办法，我会逼你们俩的... ...你会汗流浃背的。
If I come up with anything else, I'll push you both so hard... ...you'll be sweating silver bullets.
你听到了吗?
You hear me?
是的，我们听到了。
Yeah, we got ears.
如果他们把我们和酒店联系起来，我们就完了。
If they tie us to the hotel, we're done.
是的。
Yeah.
我们要赶在他们之前找到那个贱人。
We're gonna find that bitch before they do.
卖鞋的，做快餐的。
Shoe salesman, short order cook.
有许多工作向有抱负的年轻人开放。
A lot of jobs open for ambitious young men.
你玩得很开心。不是真的。
You're having fun. Not really.
让我看看法罗的笔记。我想查一下另外两个名字。
Let me see Farrow's note. I want to check those other two names.
菲利普·布莱德索，埃琳娜·科尔还有括号里的"勒罗伊先生"
Philip Bledsoe, Elena Cole and in parenthesis, a "Mr. Leroy."
只有名字，只有名字。
Just names, just names.
那我们就从电话簿开始查。
Then we start with the phone book.
我们得找到那个婊子。
We gotta find that bitch.
这样等你长大了你就会知道很多东西了。
Well, that's so when you grow up you'll know a lot of stuff.
再说了，孩子们都回学校了你一整天都要干什么?
And besides, what are you gonna do all day when the kids are back in school?
不，我不需要秘书，但如果我需要的话，就是你了。
No, I don't need a secretary, but if I ever need one, you're it.
我叫博格斯。
My name is Boggs.
我想见科尔夫人。埃琳娜·科尔。
Uh, I'd like to see Mrs. Cole. Elena Cole.
你能告诉我你想要什么吗?
Could you tell me what you want?
我想谈谈克利夫顿·法罗和玛丽·简·鲍尔。
I want to talk about Clifton Farrow and Mary Jane Bower.
请您在这里等一下好吗?
Would you mind waiting here, please.
不，你下面肯定有颗牙。
No, you must have had a tooth under there.
确定。
Sure.
那下面肯定有颗牙。
You had to have a tooth under there.
当然，每个人都知道。
Sure, everybody knows that.
牙齿越多，面包就越多。
More teeth, more bread.
你可以用棍子把他们打晕，也可以用钳子。
Well, you could knock 'em out with a stick or you could get a pair of pliers.
不用客气，亲爱的。
You're welcome, sweetheart.
我也爱你。
I love you, too.
但我不能说出来，因为太尴尬了。
Except I can't say it cause it's embarrassing.
你能让你妈妈给我打电话吗?
Will you ask your Mom to call me?
是的。请乖一点。
Yes. Please be good.
好吧，挂电话，亲爱的。
All right, hang up, dear.
好吧，再见。
All right, bye, bye.
你好。
Hello.
请这边走。
Step this way please.
伯格斯吗?
Boggs?
你这是什么名字啊，兄弟?
Now, what kind of name is that, brother?
爱尔兰人。
Irish.
黑色的爱尔兰?
Black Irish?
主要是。
Mostly.
好吧。
All right.
莱斯特。给他拿把椅子。
Lester. Get him a chair.
待在家里。
Be at home.
啊，去吧，待在家里。
Ah, go ahead, be at home.
我能为你做什么?
Now, what can I do for you?
好吧?都在角落里排队。对吧?
Okay? All lined up for the corner. Right?
保持放松。真是个好女孩。
Keep loose there. Atta girl.
现在。
Now.
她想做生意。
She wants to do business.
什么时候?
When?
今晚。
Tonight.
叫部队来。
Call the troops.
你还挺冷静的。
You're taking things pretty calm.
是的。什么发生?
Yeah. Anything happen?
我找不到布莱索。
I couldn't find Bledsoe.
我撞到了科尔夫人。
Uh, I ran down Mrs. Cole.
她有什么故事?
What's her story?
民权狂人，妇女解放运动。
Civil rights nut, women's lib.
没有孩子，寡妇。
No kids, widow.
现在正在北边试图夺回恶魔岛。
Up north at the moment trying to retake Alcatraz.
要花很多面包。
Costs a lot of bread.
足够勒罗伊先生和一屋子人吃了。
Enough to keep Mr. Leroy and a houseful of folks.
他怎么样了?
What about him?
他是他的人民的领袖。
He's the leader of his people.
哦,男人。
Oh, man.
他要把这些幸运的人带到哪里去?
And where is he leading these lucky people?
从瓦茨到贝尔艾尔的拉布雷亚河上游。
Up La Brea from Watts to Bel Air.
勒罗伊。秃头吗?
Leroy. Bald?
在家里戴墨镜?
Wears sunglasses in the house?
是的。
Yeah.
是的。重量级的。
Yeah. Heavyweight.
贫民窟巨星。
Ghetto superstar.
无论如何。
Anyway.
反正什么都没有。
Anyway nothing.
法罗为科尔夫人做了些装饰。
Farrow did some decorating of some kind for Mrs. Cole.
没人听说过玛丽·简。
Nobody ever heard of Mary Jane.
好了，我们熟了。
So, we're cooked.
我们无处可去。
We got nowhere to go.
没有客户端。
No client.
没有嫌疑人，没有线索。
No suspect, no leads.
没有线索，什么都没有。
No clues, nothing.
不管怎样，你绝对猜不到是谁打来的。
Anyway, you'll never guess who called.
谁?
Who?
玛丽简。
Mary Jane.
她今晚想见我们。
She wants to see us tonight.
说她很害怕，想放弃。
Said she's scared and wants to give up.
如果我们帮助她，我们就能得到奖励。
If we help her, why then, we can get the reward.
我会被诅咒的。
I'll be goddamned.
正确的。
Right.
但是她经常说谎。
But she lies a lot.
她怎么知道我们的电话号码的?
How the hell did she get our number?
只能来自甜蜜的双唇。所以…他找到她了，没错。
Could only come from Sweet Lips. So... He's found her, all right.
黑人社区并没有试图成为新的东西。
Black community is not trying to become something new.
其实在其行为、心理上基本上还是白色的。
Is in fact still basically white in its behavior, psychologically.
这就是为什么我的领袖，我们的领袖，一遍又一遍地说黑人权力不能嫉妒白人权力。
That's why my leader, our leader, keeps saying over and over again that black power cannot be jealous of white power.
它必须对此感到厌倦。它必须知道……绿球区32号后面有四个车位。
It has to be sick of it. It has to know... Four car spaces behind the green ball plot 32.
第八局开始。
The start of the eighth inning.
蓝色雷鸟的后座。
The back seat of the blue Thunderbird.
是的，亲爱的，她会来的。
Yes my dear, she will be there.
就像他们说的，双关语。
A punto, as they say.
完全正确。
Exactly.
它工作。
It worked.
她所有的线人都被愚蠢的怪物吓跑了。
All her sources have been frightened away by the stupid monsters.
他们并不愚蠢。
They're not stupid.
她必须按我们的价格和我们做生意。
She has to do business with us, at our price.
今晚。我说过我能行。
Tonight. I told you I can do it.
她走投无路了，那个讨厌的婊子。
She's desperate, that nasty bitch.
绝望下流的婊子很危险，兄弟。
Desperate, nasty bitches are dangerous, brother.
它会成功的。
It will work.
我派菲利普去。
I'm sending Phillip.
在阻力。
In drag.
这是八分之一的顶部。
That's the top of the eighth.
嘿。
Hey.
这是她的。
That's her.
走了。
Go.
你好。玛丽简吗?
Hello. Mary Jane?
持有它。
Hold it.
把门关上!
Shut that door!
关门，你个白痴。
Shut the door, you idiot.
停车场里有五百辆车，那群混蛋把我的炸掉了。
Five hundred cars in the lot, and the bastards blow up mine.
好吧，以牙还牙。
Well, tit for tat.
一些玛丽·简。
Some Mary Jane.
怎么啦？Bledsoe。
What? It's Bledsoe.
那个我们找不到的人。
The guy we couldn't find.
我得找把大点的枪，我什么都打不到。
I gotta get a bigger gun, I can't hit nothing.
我们怎么解释这个呢?
How we gonna explain this one?
这一次，我们需要一个律师。
Well, this time, we need a lawyer.
那个贱人陷害了我们。
That bitch set us up.
是的。
Yeah.
等待。等一下，等一下。
Wait. Wait a minute, wait a minute.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
卡赞贾默的孩子们，他们刚刚炸掉了道奇体育场。
The Katzenjammer kids, they just blew up Dodger Stadium.
又一个推销员死了。这次我们拿到了钱。
Another bagman's dead. This time we got the money.
没有女孩。他们没有击中鱼雷。
No girl. They missed the torpedoes.
他们的借口是什么?
What's their excuse?
希基说他接到了那个女孩的电话。
Hickey claims he got a call from the girl.
她说如果他们叫我们去她就不去了。
She said she wouldn't show if they called us in.
我要他们被抓。
I want them busted.
隐瞒证据，教唆犯罪行为。
Withholding evidence, abetting felonious conduct.
然后烧掉它们。把他们俩都绑起来。
And burn them. Put a stake up both of them.
今晚我就给萨克拉门托打电话，开个听证会，吊销他们的执照，把他们关起来。
Now, I'll call Sacramento tonight, set a hearing, suspend their licenses, break 'em, put 'em away.
嗯。
Mmm-hmm.
我们把所有的钱都给了他们，但我们可以留下那2000块。
We gave 'em every piece, but we could have kept that two grand.
我们把它交上去，然后去了警察局。
We turned it in and we went to the police department.
不如给我点有用的证据吧?
Well, how about giving me some evidence I can use?
如果你能把它扔出去的话。
Well, if you'd get it thrown out.
扔出去吗?
Thrown out?
我们付钱给你到底是为了什么?
What the hell do we pay you for anyway?
他们抓住了你的饼干。
They've got you by the biscuits.
找点关系什么的。
Pull some strings or something.
特朗普说点什么，行吗?
Trump something up, can't you?
我是律师，不是魔术师。
I'm a lawyer, not a magician.
我们要出庭受审吗?
We're gonna have to stand trial?
除非他们撤销指控。
Unless they drop the charges.
我不知道。
I don't know.
怎么啦？
What?
是时候出去了。
It's time to get out.
出于什么?
Out of what?
这个职业已经没有什么可干的了，弗兰克。都结束了。
There's nothing left of this profession, Frank. It's all over.
这不是关于任何事情。
It's not about anything.
嗯，他是对的。
Well, he's right.
再也没有私家侦探这回事了。
No such thing as a private investigator anymore.
随着萨克拉门托过去几年的立法，你们这些人只不过是流程服务人员。
With the legislation coming out of Sacramento the last couple of years, you guys are nothing but process servers.
这不是关于任何事情。
It's not about anything.
-是啊。-大约40万。
- Yeah, it is. - It's about 400 grand.
我们得找到那个贱人。
Well, we gotta find that bitch.
他们真的让你很为难。
They've really got you up against it.
是的。这就是所谓的推，它们在推。
Yeah. Well, that's what's known as pushing, they're pushing.
你要怎么做?
What are you gonna do?
你只需要反击，继续前进。
Just have to push back and keep going.
下班后我去你家。
I'll come to your place after work.
你会吗?
Uh, you will?
我等你。
I'll wait for you.
是的，很好。
Yeah, that's nice.
是的。情况正在好转。
Yeah. Things are looking up.
你管他们叫士兵。你管他们叫士兵。
You call them soldiers. You call them soldiers.
他们错过了。
They missed.
两辆车被炸成碎片。
Two cars blown to goddamn hell.
他们错过了。两根铅笔脖子比他强。
They missed. Outgunned by two pencil necks.
告诉我，他们怎么能这样?解释它。
Tell me, how could they? Explain it.
我想听听他们是怎么失手的。这是什么?
I want to hear how they missed. What is it?
沉默吗?黄色的?
Dumbness? Yellow?
你到底来这儿干什么?
What the hell do you come in here for?
音乐。
The music.
我想他们拿了你的啤酒。
I think they got your beer.
来吧，我们给你买辆车。
Come on, let's buy you a car.
你先是要卖掉我的房子，现在又要给我买辆车。
First you're gonna sell my house and now you're gonna buy me a car.
如果你不再管房子的事，我就给你买辆车。
I'm gonna buy you a goddamn car if you lay off about the house.
这是一个好房子。
It was a good house.
是什么。
Was.
现在依然如此。
It still is.
至少它没有掉下悬崖。
At least it's not falling off a cliff.
那你的保证呢，好让你去买保险?
Well, where's your word, so you can get the insurance for it?
太迟了，用完了。
Ah, it's too late, it ran out.
跑了出去。弗兰克，弗兰克，弗兰克，弗兰克。
Ran out. Frank, Frank, Frank, Frank.
看。
Look.
镇上所有人都要把我们烧了。
Everybody in this town is about to burn us up.
你现在不能对我坏了。
You can't go bad on me now.
弗兰克，你还不明白吗?
Frank, don't you get it?
我们的照片登在所有的报纸上。
Our pictures are in all the newspapers.
他们要把我们埋了。
They are going to bury us.
一方或另一方。
One side or the other.
伊迪丝来了。
Edith is here.
她马上就来，然后我们就走。
She'll be on in a minute and then we'll go.
我以为她被禁止进来了?
I thought she was barred from here?
那家伙欠我人情。
Guy owed me a favor.
♬站在街上
♪ Standing out on the street
♬我手里的行李箱
♪ Suitcase in my hand
♪站在大街上♪我需要一个完美的男人
♪ Standing out on the street ♪ Yes, I need a perfect man
♬我在想什么
♪ What things am I thinking
♬一切由你决定。
♪ It's up to you Eat your heart out.
♬我找不到我需要的词语♬告诉你我在做什么♬家是你的地方♬你不能玩太久
♪ I can't find the words I need ♪ To tell you what I do ♪ Home is where you make it ♪ You can't play too long
♬家就是你带它去的地方♬我已经很久没有回家了
♪ Home is where you take it ♪ I ain't been home so long
♬我在想什么
♪ What things am I thinking
♬由你决定谢谢，弗兰克。
♪ It's up to you Thanks, Frank.
杀了你自己。
Kill yourself.
我们要去哪里?我们要去哪里?
Where do we go? Where do we go?
在大街上。
Out on the street.
玛丽·简不会再给我们打电话了。
Mary Jane isn't gonna call us any more.
她这么做是为了什么?
What's she doing it for?
重磅炸弹和我们。
The heavies and us.
我们在推她。
We're pushing her.
她觉得不管我们死了谁，她都好。
She figures whichever one of us is dead, she's better off.
她牺牲了两个推销员。
She sacrificed two bagmen.
也就是说她有人可以卖给她。你能看见吗?
That means she's got somebody to sell it to. Can you see?
玛丽·简和花店老板的哥哥有一笔大交易。
Mary Jane had a big deal with the florist's brother.
监狱里的那个，他在奇诺。
The one in jail, he's at Chino.
我明天早上要去那里，四处看看。
I'm going down there tomorrow morning, poke around.
你还缺一辆车。
You're still short one car.
是的，我会想办法的。
Yeah, I'll work something out.
你呢?
What about you?
我会从海边的房子开始。
I'll start with the house at the beach.
最后一轮。这是正确的。
Last go round. That's right.
你能看见吗?
Can you see?
它是如何运行的?
How does it run?
棒极了。
Terrific.
我买了。
I'll take it.
是的。
Yeah.
听着，鱼雷击中了我家。
Yeah, listen, the torpedoes hit my place.
把它拆开了。他们可能正在来找你的路上。
Pulled it apart. They may be on their way to see you.
他们没有什么目的，没有。
They weren't after anything, not really.
这不是一份好工作。
It's not a good job.
他们乐在其中，就像复仇一样。
They got a kick out of it, like revenge.
他们已经来过了。
They've already been here.
该死的大学生们，大半夜的，我们要打扫房子。
Goddamn college boys, in the middle of the night, we're gonna clean house.
他走了进来。
He walked in.
他说他想回家。
He says he wants to come home.
我认为他是对的。
I think he's right.
但我也认为他欠我们很多利息。
But I also think he owes us a lot of interest.
我觉得他还欠我们一笔奖金。
I think he owes us another bonus.
他们说，我们必须完成它。
They said, we have to go through with it.
赖斯和那个黑人的交易。
The deal with Rice and the black man.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
妮欧娜不在这里。
Nyona's not here.
她死了，是你杀了她。
She's dead and you killed her.
我不希望你再和这个孩子在一起。
And I don't want you around this child ever again.
你是个烂……
You're a rotten...
从两年前你走进这间房子的那一刻起我就知道你是个卑鄙下流的混蛋。
I know from the moment you walked into this house two years ago that you're a rotten, low down, son-of-a-bitch.
我是认真的。
And I mean it.
我再也不想见到你了。
I don't ever want to see your face again.
了。
Ever again.
都准备好了吗?
Is it all set?
是的。
Yep.
好。
Good.
不会再失手了。不要再犯错了。
No more misses. No more mistakes.
好吧。
All right.
你没事吧?
You all right?
好。
Good.
我去过中国。
I've been to Chino.
奎曼多是前天假释出来的。
Quemando got out, on parole, day before yesterday.
一个女人遇见了他。
A woman met him.
她登记的名字是玛丽·弗罗里达·奎曼多。
She signed in as Mary Florida Quemando.
的妻子。
Wife.
宾果。
Bingo.
我从假释官那里得到了他们的地址。
I got their address from the parole officer.
好了，我们开始吧。
So, okay, we're in business.
我们去找他们吧。
Let's go get 'em.
我知道你想要鱼雷。
I know you want the torpedoes.
我们找到那个女人，他们就在附近。
We find the woman, they're gonna be close.
哦，该死的，他们不会进来的。
Oh, look goddammit, they're not coming in here.
这是一个机会。
It's a chance.
好吧，你不干了。
Okay, you quit.
很好。
Fine.
躺下，在这里滚一滚。
Just lay down and roll over right here.
这是个适合你做的好地方。
It's a nice place for you to do it.
至少我们不会渴了。
At least we're not going to be thirsty.
鲍勃。
Bob.
我们来一个。就在这儿。
Let's have one. Right here please.
因为我要加入我的朋友兼搭档。
Because I'm joining my friend and partner.
哦,弗兰克。
Oh, Frank.
弗兰克，你现在不能对我发脾气。
Frank, you can't go bad on me now.
他们会把我们埋了。
They're gonna bury us.
就因为你没法把这个愚蠢，愚蠢，可怜的婊子从你肚子里赶出去。
Just because you can't get this dumb, stupid, pitiful bitch out of your guts.
看看是谁在说话。
Look who's talking.
你就坐在那，我去拿。
You just sit there 'cause I'm gonna go get them.
我想要那25。
I want that 25.
你可以在那里坐很长时间，但你不能让她回来。
You can sit there for a long time, but you can't bring her back.
你无法弥补你错过的。
And you can't make up for what you missed.
所有……
All...
你唯一能做的就是
Only thing you can do is
该死的，尽量扯平。
goddamn try to even it up.
纠正错误。
Make it right.
现在我要出去，我要抓住他们。所以…
Now I'm going out there and I'm gonna get 'em. So...
现在你告诉我她在哪。
Now you tell me where she is.
告诉我她在哪，不然我就杀了你。
Tell me where she is or I'm gonna kill you.
他会的。
He will.
不要沮丧。你没什么好哭的。
Don't be depressed. You got nothing to cry about.
在监狱里策划一场价值40万美元的越狱是非常困难的。
It's very difficult to run a $400,000 caper from a prison cell.
你做得很好。
You did pretty good.
你还有玛丽·简。
You still got Mary Jane.
她一定是个了不起的女人。
She must be a heck of a woman.
替你杀了法罗，因为他想要更大的份额，在你出狱之前一直掌控大局。
Killed Farrow for you cause he wanted a bigger bite, ran the whole show till you got out.
她真是个好女人。
She's one hell of a woman.
你们俩当然会被起诉，但这太牵强了，他们站不住脚。
Course you'll both be indicted, but it's too shaky, they won't make it stick.
所以…也许你还能回家。
So... Maybe you'll still get home.
他是在告诉你情况可能会更糟。
He's telling you things could be a whole lot worse.
想想看。
Think about it.
赖斯先生，跟博格斯先生打个招呼。
Mr. Rice, say hello to Mr. Boggs.
莱斯先生。
Mr. Rice.
勒罗伊先生。
Mr. Leroy.
跟希基先生打个招呼。
Say hello to Mr. Hickey.
真是一落千丈啊?
It really fell off the cliff, huh?
真遗憾，但我的搭档跟你做了笔好交易。
That's a shame, but my partner has a hell of a deal for you.
房子很棒，周围环境也不错。
Terrific house, fine neighborhood.
你听他的。
You listen to him.
你就照希基先生说的做。
You just do what Mr. Hickey tells you.
我要按照设定的那样做。
I'm gonna do everything just as it was set up.
好吧?
Okay?
好吧，勒罗伊先生?
Okay, Mr. Leroy?
这是你的游戏，兄弟。
It's your play, brother.
你怎么选这个地方的?
How'd you pick this place?
我们过去常来这里。
We used to come here.
好了，出去准备好。
Okay, get out there and get ready.
把她放下来，就像一切正常一样。
Wave her down just like everything was all right.
把这个包带走。
Take the bag with you.
没人来了。
Nobody came.
没有人在乎。
Nobody cares.
谢谢。
Thanks.
任何时候。
Anytime.
这仍然不是关于任何事情。
It's still not about anything.
我知道，你告诉过我。
Yeah, I know, you told me.
♬我从来没有想过筹码会掉下来♬我一直相信比赛很难赢♬我看到的东西♬我去过的地方追逐我的梦想
♪ Oh, I never thought the chips would fall away ♪ Have always believed the game was hard to win ♪ Things I've seen ♪ The places I have been to chase my dreams
♪走进阳光，我们将走进阳光
♪ Into the sun, we will walk into the sun
♬谈谈我们想做的事♬忘记我们这辈子做过的事
♪ And talk about the things we'd like to do ♪ Forgetting what we've done in our time
过去的已经过去了
♪ What's past is dead and gone
♬没有时间悲伤，世界上太多悲伤了♬是时候在梦想破灭之前生活了♬哦，是的在梦想破灭之前
♪ There's no time to grieve, too much sorrow in the world ♪ It's time to live before the dream is through ♪ Oh, yes ♪ Before the dream is through
♬我从来没有想过筹码会落在我的路上♬我一直相信♬比赛很难赢♬我见过的东西♬我去过的地方追逐我的梦想♬
♪ Oh, I never thought the chips would fall my way ♪ I've always believed ♪ The game is hard to win ♪ Things I've seen ♪ The places I have been to chase my dreams ♪